infogurushop.com 2015-10-26

# Privacy Policy | Infogurushop

Video Directory, 1 Stop Mobile, Multimedia, Multichannel Advertising. Local, National or Global across all devices. 

Infogurushop.Com is owned and operated by Infogurushop Ltd.  
Infogurushop is committed to protecting your privacy. We do NOT track or collect visitors information. We only collect ‘members or paid clients’ name, address, phone, email, website or social media links etc to enhance your overall Infoguruhop experience and to inform you of any features and offers and or to develop our service so that it exceeds our paid customers’ expectations. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.

Before you provide any personal information to us, please ensure that you read and agree to all the Terms contained in this Privacy Policy and our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.infogurushop.com/terms-conditions/) in particular Term 4 and our Feedback Policy. If you do not agree with any of the Terms please do not provide any information and please stop using the Website immediately. By providing your Personal Information, you will be deemed to consent to us obtaining, holding, using, sharing or otherwise processing your Personal Information or contacting you in relation to any of the purposes permitted or authorised by this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.

**Information we collect and how we use it**  
Registration is NOT compulsory to browse or use many features of the Website, however, we encourage you to register with us to enable you to make full use of the Website and to provide feedback, receive updates and information from IGS. When you register, we will ask you to provide your name, e-mail and contact address or number for business reasons. This will be your log in detail and an e-mail confirmation and verification procedure will follow to authenticate who you are. If you know or suspect that someone else may be using your e-mail address fraudulently you should notify us by contacting Customer Services at gurushop1[at]zoho.com immediately. You must confirm your e-mail address before any feedback can be published to ensure that your feedback is genuine. We may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to the website, new Infoguruhop services and special offers we think will be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please let us know by e-mail on gurushop1[at]zoho.com. Infogurushop welcomes and upholds the [Universal Human Rights Declaration](https://www.un.org/en/documents/udhr/).

**Protection of Customer Information**  
As required by The Data Protection Act 1998, we have security procedures in place which deal with the storage and disclosure of personal information that you have given us and to prevent unauthorised access to that personal information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose information to you.

**Disclosure of collected information to outside parties**  
Any Personal Information supplied by you will only be held and used by ourselves in accordance with our Privacy Policy and we will not use or pass on your details to any third party without your consent except to enable us to process or to fulfil your order, or as is otherwise permitted or authorised by the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.infogurushop.com/terms-conditions/) (including our Privacy Policy).

Infogurushop does NOT sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. Infogurushop may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, website users, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. Please note that in the event that any personal information is contained in the comments sections of the feedback form, this may be published and used in accordance with our Feedback Policy and would be available to outside parties. We strongly recommend that you do not include any information in the feedback comments by which you could be personally identified.

**Sale of business**  
If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

**Your Consent**  
By registering with Infogurushop and/or using our website or service, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Infogurushop Ltd in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the website at www.infogurushop.com so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. If at any time you wish to cancel your registration with us, please email us at gurushop1[at]zoho.com We can remove your details from our active database, although some information may remain in our archives.

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
